TERRANCE PLEASANT

pleasant.terrance@gmail.com | 408.375.1256 | Henderson, NV 89002

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I possess 20+ years of IT Support and Networking connectivity. Utilizing system administrator and networking platforms in a wide range of business applications. My objectives are to reduce system errors and failures through networking tracking methods based upon industry leading practices.

OBJECTIVE

I am seeking a Senior Desktop Administrator position.

STRENGTHS

My recognized strengths include critical thinking, problem solving and leadership skills within cross-functional teams. Through these teams we achieved business unit goals by developing standard operating procedures using critical analysis and prioritizing incoming requests and alerts to optimize IT system dynamic usage rates. Leveraging problem solving methods at first, second, and third level support to resolve difficult, complex, and sensitive IT matters. Providing data driven guidance on how to track and develop documentation. Supported by deep technical expertise to resolve complex problems simultaneously meeting customer expectations.

SKILLS

- Team Leader
- Communications
- Mac systems
- Customer service expert
- Software Installation
- IT Support
- Network Troubleshooting
- System upgrades

- MS Office
- Desktop support
- TCP/IP
- Troubleshooting and Diagnostics
- Technical Support
- Hardware Troubleshooting
- Hardware and software installation

WORK HISTORY

Senior Desktop Support / Zenith Technologies - Las Vegas, NV / 08.2019 - 03.2020

• Followed up with clients to verify optimal customer

satisfaction following support engagement and problem resolution.

- Appropriated on average of 40 phone calls on help desk
- Created user accounts in active directory and Micro soft exchange
- Imaged laptops and desktops using Ghost
- Web Ex administrator
- Responsible for managing assets via Solarwinds

Team Lead Desktop Support / Applied Materials | San Jose, CA / 06.2018 - 07.2019

- Responsible for managing the que for a team of 17.
- Responsible for managing desktop teams' calendar.
- Reported teams Metrix in weekly Ops meeting.
- Responsible for assisting technician for any escalation issues.
- Maintained an updated documentation for the team.
- Held weekly meetings with the tech team to discuss the Metrix.
- Lead the team in Refresh project upgrading 1500 laptops OS.

Team Lead | Itron | San Jose, CA | May7 2018 – Feb / Itron - San Jose, CA / 05.2018 - 02.2019

- Managed team of 5 in implementing process of Upgrading OS Win7,8.1 to Win10 and moving 1200 computer to new domain via Vbscript.
- Responsible for imaging computers using Sccm.
- Deployed applications using Sccm, as well as asset management.
- Responsible implementing process of Upgrading OS and moving 1200 computers to a new domain via Vbscript.
- Set up and supported MS office 365
- Setup and configured One drive
- Upgraded Os Win 7, 8.1 to windows 10
- Documented process of upgrading Os in SharePoint.

System Administrator / Depomed - Fremont, CA / 01.2018 - 05.2018

- Executive support for Directors and their admins both software and hardware issues.
- Provided onsite 2nd level and remote support for end users.

- Responsible for imaging computers using Sccm.
- Deployed applications using Sccm, as well as asset management.
- Responsible for troubleshooting hardware software problems for both Macs and PC's Responsible for managing hardware.
- Supported Office 365.
- Created user accounts.
- Responsible for managing the onboard process. Creating end users accounts.
- Responsible for managing the off boarding.

EDUCATION

San Jose City College - San Jose, CA

CERTIFICATIONS

ITIL Certification - 2014